## Juan David Lizarralde Niño

Full Stack Developer

React Js | Node Js | Express Js | Mongo DB | AWS | GitHub

Visual & Multimedia professional.

Four years of experience in Audiovisual Marketing. With more than two years of experience in Web Development. I worked in a company and now as a freelance. My dream is to help with my knowledge, and my energy. I want to grow up in my career and resolve problems in the development world

Bogotá, Colombia
(57) 310 755 9990
juand.lizarralden@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/juandal
nino
https://github.com/JUANDAL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Freelance** — Full Stack Developer

DEC 2021 - PRESENT

- Collaborated with the team to design, structure, and implement new websites from start to finish.
- Updated existing websites
- Developed a user-friendly architecture, and provided support and customer services.
- Worked with MERN stack.

## TEDI, Colombia — Web Developer

JAN 2020 - JUN 2022

- Design and develop the official web page for TEDI (2020)
- Modified HTML, JS, and CSS web pages to optimize the page's performance for faster loading and browsing
- E-mail developer, responsible for developing email, using HTML, CSS, and media queries.
- Utilized strategic engineering procedures to maintain and improve the company's web application

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Universidad Jorge Tadeo Lozano,** Colombia — Bachelor of Film and MultiMedia

JAN 2014 - DEC 2018

**IBM** — DevOps, Cloud, and Agile Foundations Specialization MAR 2022 - JUL 2022

**freeCodeCamp** — Legacy Full Stack Certification

DEC 2021 - DEC 2023

#### **SKILLS**

**NINO** 

- Cloud Computing
- Web Application & Development
- Data base & Servers
- Proficient Troubleshooting
- Technical Process Improvement

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

DevOps, Cloud, and Agile Foundations | IBM 2022

Responsive Web Design | freeCodeCamp 2022

JavaScript Developer | CoderHouse 2022

#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish native English professional (B2)